http://pixintl.com/privacypolicy%2020180523.htm

pix724.com pixintl.com Privacy Policy Information Collection
Our Contact Information This
privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are
concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is
being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information
security, is information that can be used on its own or with other
information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to
identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy
carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect
or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in
accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When
ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked
to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or
other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We
collect information from you when you register on our site, place an
order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form
or enter information on our site.Provide us with feedback on our products or services
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make
a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or
marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site
features in the following ways:      •
To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of
content and product offerings in which you are most interested.      • To improve our website in order to better serve you.      • To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.      • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.      • To quickly process your transactions.      • To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products      • To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)How do we protect your information?We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.We do not use Malware Scanning.We do not use an SSL certificate      •
We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or
private information like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers.Do we use 'cookies'?Yes.
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)
that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we
use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping
cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based
on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you
with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile
aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can
offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We use cookies to:      • Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.      • Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.      • Keep track of advertisements.      •
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in
order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may
also use trusted third-party services that track this information on
our behalf.You can choose to have your
computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose
to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings.
Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu
to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If users disable cookies in their browser:If you turn cookies off it will turn off some of the features of the site.Third-party disclosureWe
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with
advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and
other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep
this information confidential. We may also release information when
it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site
policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be
provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Third-party linksOccasionally,
at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or
services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and
independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or
liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.
Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome
any feedback about these sites.GoogleGoogle's
advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising
Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for
users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.Google,
as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users
based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google
Ad and Content Network privacy policy.We have implemented the following:      • Remarketing with Google AdSense      • Google Display Network Impression Reporting      • Demographics and Interests Reporting      • DoubleClick Platform IntegrationWe,
along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies
(such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as
the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to
compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other
ad service functions as they relate to our website. Opting out:Users
can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google
Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the
Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google
Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA
is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and
online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches
well beyond California to require any person or company in the United
States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting
Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a
conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the
information being collected and those individuals or companies with
whom it is being shared. - See more at:
http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously.Once
this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home
page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our
website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:      • On our Privacy Policy PageCan change your personal information:      • By emailing usHow does our site handle Do Not Track signals?We
honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use
advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral trackingCOPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When
it comes to the collection of personal information from children under
the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
(COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United
States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which
spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to
protect children's privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.Fair Information PracticesThe
Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law
in the United States and the concepts they include have played a
significant role in the development of data protection laws around the
globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how
they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various
privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify you via email      • Within 7 business daysWe
also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that
individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against
data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This
principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights
against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts
or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance
by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe
CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email,
establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the
right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out
tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:      • Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions      • Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:      • Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.      • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.      • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.      • Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.      • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.      • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us atremove@pix724.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.pix724.com pixintl.comPO Box 10532Chicago, IL 60610-0532 USAeditorial@pixintl.comLast Edited on 2018-05-23
